kidslivesafe.com 2013-10-05

# Privacy Policy

**OUR COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY** Last updated: October, 2012 KidsLiveSafe.com is a website owned and operated by Kids Live Safe, LLC ("we"or "us"). We understand how important your privacy is to you, so we are committed to assuring your privacy. This page outlines all of the steps we take to protect your privacy and what we do with your information that you provide to us through our web site. **KIDSLIVESAFE.COM PRIVACY PLEDGE:** We do not collect any personal information from you that you do not volunteer, and we are the sole owner of all information collected on this site. We fully disclose our privacy policy in this document. If you have any questions or comments, you are invited to contact us.    **PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION:** We use SSL-encryption technology when transferring and receiving consumer data on our and our affiliates' websites to protect your personal information. We have partnered with VeriSign or other equally reliable encryption services to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you. The servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment. However, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this site cannot be guaranteed; and any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party. We make no warranty, express, implied, or otherwise, that we will prevent unauthorized access to your private information.   **WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT:** In order to provide you with our services, we collect two types of information about our users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.    **PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION:  ** This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as registering for a membership, ordering or utilizing a product or service, or sending us feedback, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), email address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, assets, liabilities, and other personal identifying information. When ordering products or services on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit or debit card number. Depending upon the product or service, if you do not provide the requested information, you may not be able to obtain the product or service you want. You should be aware that if you enter any personal information during the information request process and then hit the “continue” button on that page, the information you have entered will be transmitted to us, even though you may not complete the process on subsequent pages. Enrollment in any KidsLiveSafe.com service is contingent upon your agreeing to the Terms of Use of membership and providing personally identifiable information as described above.    **NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION:** This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit on our site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. This information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet.    **HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT:** We will use Personally Identifiable Information to enhance the operation of our site, fill orders, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, statistically analyze site use, improve our product and service offerings, and customize our site's content, layout, and services. We may use Personally Identifiable Information to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding administrative notices. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our agreements with you, including our Terms of Use, Disclaimer, and this Privacy Policy. Your information may also be used by us or by third parties to whom we transfer it to provide the products or services you have requested.

When you use our site we will store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use of our site. A cookie is a small data text file, which a Web site stores on your computer's hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. The cookies make your use of the site easier, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our site may not work properly in that case.

We may use an outside ad serving company to display banner advertisements on our site. As part of their service, they will place a separate cookie on your computer. We will not provide any such third-party ad server with your Personally Identifiable Information. In addition, other advertisers may also place banner ads on our site, and we will not disclose any Personally Identifiable Information to them.

We and our third party ad server may collect and use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about you, such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server and whether you responded to a particular ad. 

  **WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION:** Other than your credit or debit card information (which we will only share with third parties as described below), we may share your Personally Identifiable Information with third parties in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy and applicable state and federal law. We provide the products and services offered on our website through contractual arrangements with affiliates, service providers, and other third parties. We and such third parties use your Personally Identifiable Information to operate our sites and to deliver their products and services.

For example, we must release your credit card or debit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for products and services purchased on this site; release your Personally Identifiable Information to the third party that will provide the products or services that you ordered; and provide order information to third parties that help us provide customer service. We will encourage our service providers to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by our service providers is governed by the privacy policies of those service providers, and is not subject to our control.

We may also provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers' sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to third party advertisers, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information.

Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.

From time to time we will send you email newsletters and updates announcing special offers and/or new features as well as materials that are promotional in nature. These email updates may also include offers from our marketing partners that you may be interested in. As part of our service you will receive these updates. If you want to update your email address or stop receiving any of the updates, follow the unsubscribe procedures at the bottom of any newsletter or update we send you. 

  **PRIVACY POLICY OF THIRD PARTIES:** When you sign-up for services through our site, keep in mind you will be interacting with a third party that operates under its own privacy and security policies. Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses our use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other sites accessible through our site, and companies to whom your information is transferred, have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Additionally, other companies that place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect. You should also be aware that unsubscribing from us will not automatically unsubscribe you from third parties’ lists and/or databases. _If you wish to opt-out of third party offers, please email us at_[ _optout@kidslivesafe.net_](mailto:optout@kidslivesafe.net) _and we will make commercially reasonable efforts to have your email removed the they list of our 3rd Parties._   **BUSINESS TRANSACTIONS:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, customer information (both Personally Identifiable and Non-Personally Identifiable Information) may be one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that we, or substantially all of our assets, are acquired, such customer information will be included within the transferred assets.    **OPTING OUT:** If you no longer wish to receive our emails, newsletter or promotional offers, you may "opt-out" of receiving these communications by opting-out on our unsubscribe page or by clicking here to unsubscribe. Please note that opting not to receive email does not exempt you from receiving administrative emails, which include but are not limited to, notices about membership status changes and alterations to our Terms of Use.    **CHANGES TO OUR POLICY:** We may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it frequently. When we do, we will post those changes on this page and update the effective date so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of our Site Terms of Use, and by accessing or using our site, you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to maintain a valid email address as a registered user, review this site and this Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. Your use of the site after such modifications will constitute your acknowledgment of the modified Policy; and agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Policy. 

  **MISCELLANEOUS/CONTACT INFORMATION:**

_You must be at least 18 years old to use this site. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personally Identifiable Information about visitors who are under 18 years of age._

_The site and its services do not provide information for purposes governed by the Fair Credit Reporting Act._

_The Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In the future, we may also make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information._

_  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
_  
Kids Live Safe  
Attn: Member Support   
3905 State Street, Suite 7-228  
Santa Barbara, CA 93105

We are available to you during normal business hours to answer any privacy-related questions or concerns you might have.

Thank you for becoming familiar with the Kids Live Safe privacy policy. You can always [contact us](http://www.kidslivesafe.com/contact-us) with any questions.

**OTHER INTERNET PRIVACY RESOURCES:** We invite you to learn more about your privacy rights on the Internet. The following resources provide an array of information and services you might find helpful and informative. Electronic Privacy and Information Center (EPIC) EPIC is a public interest research center in Washington, DC. Established in 1994, EPIC works in association with Privacy International, an international human rights group based in London, and is a member of the Global Internet Liberty Campaign and the Internet Privacy Coalition. The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) The Federal Trade Commission enforces a variety of federal antitrust and consumer protection laws. The commission works to enhance the smooth operation of the marketplace by eliminating acts or practices that are unfair or deceptive. National Fraud Information Center (NFIC) The National Fraud Information Center is a project of the National Consumers League, America's oldest nonprofit consumer organization. NFIC helps consumers report fraud and offers advice on how to avoid being victimized. The Privacy Rights Clearinghouse (PRC) PRC provides consumers with valuable information on protecting their personal privacy. ** **
